{"questions":[{"question":"Which of the following best describes \"head arrangement\" as the term is used in line 11?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"A published version of a gospel song produced for use by Black singers"},{"key":"B","answer":"A gospel song based on a slave spiritual"},{"key":"C","answer":"A musical score shared by a gospel singer and a  jazz musician"},{"key":"D","answer":"An informally written composition intended for  use by a gospel singer"},{"key":"E","answer":"An improvised performance inspired by the  singer's emotions"}],"right":["E"],"parent":0},{"question":"The author mentions \"folk fashion\" (line 4) most likely in order to","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"counter an assertion about the role of improvisation in music created by Black people"},{"key":"B","answer":"compare early gospel music with gospel music written later in the twentieth century"},{"key":"C","answer":"make a distinction between gospel music and slave spirituals"},{"key":"D","answer":"introduce a discussion about the dissemination of slave spirituals"},{"key":"E","answer":"describe a similarity between gospel music and slave spirituals"}],"right":["C"],"parent":0},{"question":"The passage suggests which of the following about Black gospel music and slave spirituals?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Both became widely known in the early twentieth century."},{"key":"B","answer":"Both had an important improvisatory element."},{"key":"C","answer":"Both were frequently performed by jazz musicians."},{"key":"D","answer":"Both were published with only a vocal line and piano accompaniment."},{"key":"E","answer":"Both were disseminated chiefly by Black singing groups."}],"right":["B"],"parent":0},{"question":"Of the following sentences, which is most likely to have immediately preceded the passage?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Few composers of gospel music drew on traditions such as the spiritual in creating their songs."},{"key":"B","answer":"Spirituals and Black gospel music were derived from the same musical tradition."},{"key":"C","answer":"The creation and singing of spirituals, practiced by Black Americans before the Civil War, continued after the war."},{"key":"D","answer":"Spirituals and gospel music can be clearly distinguished from one another."},{"key":"E","answer":"Improvisation was one of the primary characteristics of the gospel music created by Black musicians."}],"right":["B"],"parent":0},{"question":"The author of the passage is primarily concerned with","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"describing how the principles of classical chemistry were developed"},{"key":"B","answer":"initiating a debate about the kinds of chemical reactions required for the development of life"},{"key":"C","answer":"explaining how current research in chemistry may be related to broader biological concerns"},{"key":"D","answer":"reconciling opposing theories about chemical reactions"},{"key":"E","answer":"clarifying inherent ambiguities in the laws of classical chemistry"}],"right":["C"],"parent":1},{"question":"According tothe passage, classical chemical reactions and tunneling reactions are alike in which of the following ways?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"In both types of reactions, reacting molecules have to rise over the barrier between the two wells."},{"key":"B","answer":"In both types of reactions, a transition is made from the bottom of one potential well to the bottom of another."},{"key":"C","answer":"In neither type of reaction does the height of the barrier between the wells remain constant."},{"key":"D","answer":"In neither type of reaction does the rate of a chemical reaction depend on its activation energy."},{"key":"E","answer":"In both types of reactions, reacting molecules are able to go through the barrier between the two wells."}],"right":["B"],"parent":1},{"question":"According to the Arrhenius equation as discussed in the passage, which of the following statements about chemical reactions is true?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Chemical reactions are less likely to occur at temperatures close to absolute zero."},{"key":"B","answer":"In some cases the rate of a chemical reaction is related to temperature and in other cases it is not."},{"key":"C","answer":"Chemical reactions frequently occur at a few degrees above absolute zero, but they are very unpredictable."},{"key":"D","answer":"The rate of a chemical reaction depends on many other factors besides temperature."},{"key":"E","answer":"Chemical reaction rate and temperature are not related."}],"right":["A"],"parent":1},{"question":"The author's attitude toward the theory of a cold prehistory of life can best be described as","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"neutral"},{"key":"B","answer":"skeptical"},{"key":"C","answer":"mildly positive"},{"key":"D","answer":"very supportive"},{"key":"E","answer":"pointedly critical"}],"right":["C"],"parent":1},{"question":"The author's hypothesis concerning be cold prehistory of life would be most weakened if which of the following were true?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Cosmic rays are unlikely to trigger the formation of simple molecules."},{"key":"B","answer":"Tunneling occurs only in a narrow band of temperatures around zero degrees Kelvin."},{"key":"C","answer":"The synthesis of interstellar formaldehyde can be activated by means other than cosmic rays."},{"key":"D","answer":"Simple molecules can be synthesized by means of tunneling."},{"key":"E","answer":"Classical chemical reactionsdo not occur at temperatures close to absolute zero."}],"right":["A"],"parent":1},{"question":"Which of the following best describes the hypothesis of Hoyle and Wickramasinghe as it is presented in the passage?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"Cosmic rays can directly synthesize complex organic molecules."},{"key":"B","answer":"The galactic clouds are the places where prebiological evolution of compounds necessary to life occurred."},{"key":"C","answer":"Interstellar formaldehyde can be synthesized by tunneling."},{"key":"D","answer":"Molecules of interstellar formaldehyde can evolve into complex organic molecules."},{"key":"E","answer":"Complex organic molecules can be synthesized from stable polysaccharides such as cellulose and starch."}],"right":["D"],"parent":1},{"question":"Which of the following best describes the organization of the first two paragraphs of the passage?","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"The author cites a basic principle of classical chemistry and then describes the research from which that principle was developed."},{"key":"B","answer":"The author cites an apparent contradiction to the principles of classical chemistry and then explains the process of a chemical reaction to show there is in fact no contradiction."},{"key":"C","answer":"the author describes the role of heat in chemical reactions and then offers a detailed explanation of its function."},{"key":"D","answer":"The author presents a law of classical chemistry in order to introduce a kind of chemical reaction that differs from it and then explains the essential difference between the two."},{"key":"E","answer":"The author presents the fundamental rules of classical chemistry in order to introduce an explanation of a specific chemical reaction. "}],"right":["D"],"parent":1}],"parent":[]}